// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "A linear list of elements in which deletion can be done from one end (front) and insertion can take place only at the other end (rear) is known as ___________",
    answer: "Queue",
    options: [
      "Queue",
      "Stack",
      "Tree",
      "Linked list"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "In a Queue, if a user tries to remove an element from empty Queue it is called _________.",
    answer: "Underflow",
    options: [
      "Underflow",
      "Empty collection",
      "Overflow",
      "Garbage Collection"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "How many stacks are needed to implement a queue? Consider the situation where no other data structure like arrays, linked list is available to you.",
    answer: "2",
    options: [
      "1",
      "2",
      "3",
      "4"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "If the elements A, B, C and D are placed in a queue and are deleted one at a time, in what order will they be removed?",
    answer: "ABCD",
    options: [
      "ABCD",
      "DCBA",
      "DBAC",
      "ABDC"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of the following is not an advantage of a priority queue?",
    answer: "Easy to delete elements in any case",
    options: [
      "Easy to implement",
      "Processes with different priority can be efficiently handled",
      "Applications with differing requirements",
      "Easy to delete elements in any case"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Your Question is Here",
    answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
    options: [
      "Option 1",
      "option 2",
      "option 3",
      "option 4"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "In case of insertion into a linked queue, a node borrowed from the __________ list is inserted in the queue?",
    answer: "AVAIL",
    options: [
      "AVAIL",
      "FRONT",
      "REAR",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which one of the following is an application of Queue Data Structure?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "When a resource is shared among multiple consumers.",
      "When data is transferred asynchronously between two processes",
      "Load Balancing",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What is the time complexity to insert a node based on key in a priority queue?",
    answer: "O(n)",
    options: [
      "O(nlogn)",
      "O(logn)",
      "O(n)",
      "O(n^2)"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Consider a standard Circular Queue q implementation whose size is 11 and the elements of the queue are q[0], q[1], q[2]â€¦..,q[10].The front and rear pointers are initialized to point at q[2] . In which position will the ninth element be added?",
    answer: "q[0]",
    options: [
      "q[0]",
      "q[1]",
      "q[9]",
      "q[10]"
    ]
  },
];